Previously on Two and a Half Men...
Hi Charlie.
You should know that
I didn't come over to ruin your date.
Really. Why did you come over?
To tell you that I'm getting married.
Today's the big day, huh?
Oh, please.
There's no wedding.
Would it make
a difference to you,
knowing that cute little face
will never pop up
over that railing again?
That the one woman who's always
loved you and been there for you
is forever out of reach?
Come on.
Where are we going?
To the church.
I'm going to prove to you
that she's not getting married.
Look. Tell me if
you see a wedding.
I see a wedding.
OFFICIANT: Two persons
present now come to be joined.
Rose and Manfred...
She's really doing it.
...let him speak now,
or forever hold his peace.
And we're clear.
Yep, that ought to do it.
Thanks, Freddie.
♪ Men. ♪
Eenie, meenie, miney, moe.
Catch a tiger...
Oh, who am I kidding?
I love you all.
Let's see. What else do we need?
Oh, right. Ice.
Water in a useful form.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Everybody all right?
Charlie?
Rose?
What a nice surprise.
(smooches)
How are you?
Good. Good. Good.
You look great.
Oh, thank you.
Married life agrees with me.
Oh, that's right.
Congratulations.
So where are
you living now?
Uh, Manny and I moved
into my beach house.
Oh, so we'll be
neighbors again.
Yeah.
I'll have to come by
and meet him sometime.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
The old boyfriend
meeting the new husband.
It's a little awkward.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I've never been that
popular with husbands.
Or fathers.
Or boyfriends. Sons.
Surly lesbian roommates.
(sighs)
So, anyway, you're happy?
More than I ever
dreamed possible.
You know what he said
to me the other day?
Without me at his side,
he might as well not exist.
Wow. That's a little gay,
but all right.
What about you, Charlie?
Is there anyone
special in your life?
No. Not really. I mean, there's
gals with special skills,
but I got to pay extra.
You should find
someone who loves you
the way Manny loves me.
The love is the same.
It's just at an hourly rate.
Don't grow old alone, Charlie.
Right.
Bye.
What is it with women?
They go off and get married,
and all of a sudden seem
a lot more beautiful.
Ah, no matter, MacTavich.
We can grow old together.
After all, you're only 20.
But I doubt you're gonna see 21.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 8x14 ♪
Lookin' for Japanese Subs
Original Air Date on January 17, 2010
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
♪ Men. ♪
Is it on?
I think so.
All right, let's do this.
Hi. I'm Jake Harper,
and this is the Human Volcano.
We begin by drinking
a warm can of Diet Coke.
That's not Coke, dude.
Yeah. My dad did the shopping.
Anyway, a warm
diet cola product.
Ah.
And now I will swallow a Mentos.
Mentos.
(gags, sighs)
Now I will lay on the floor.
Goggles.
Right. Safety first.
You feel anything yet?
Oh, yeah. It's working.
If it starts coming
out the back door,
pull your pants down
and roll over.
Good thinking.
ALAN:
Hey, what's going on?
Not a good time, Dad.
What are you doing on the floor?
(vomiting forcefully)
Whoa! Whoa!
Awesome!
(spluttering)
What the hell are you doing?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Yeah. We were just
making a video. Hold on.
(retching)
Cool stunts.
Cool stunts?
In God's name, why?
- You've heard of Jackass?
- Yeah.
We are Dumbass.
Really?
However did you come
up with that name?
Well, we were thinking
"What's better than Jackass?"
That's kind of a
rhetorical question.
No. It wasn't that hard.
It came down to a choice
between Dumbass
and The Asskateers.
I think you made
the right call.
Really?
Oh, yes. I applaud
your decision.
The plan is, we shoot
a bunch of cool stunts,
post them online,
and then sell advertising.
Who on earth
would advertise on that?
Well, right off the bat,
we figure Coke and Mentos.
It's a product
placement bonanza.
Come on, let's go upload
our premiere episode.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What about this mess?
(sighs)
Damn it.
I'm gonna be taking care
of that kid till I'm 90.
Please, God, don't
make me live that long.
You'll never guess who I
ran into at the supermarket.
Rose.
Oh. She's back
from her honeymoon?
Yep, and living down the beach
with her new husband.
Ah, good for her.
Yeah, good for her.
You have to forget about her,
Charlie.
I know.
That's why I got me
some milk of amnesia.
Nice.
What are you
doing down there?
Wiping up cola vomit
my son spewed in my face.
Oh, great. The Human
Volcano worked.
You knew about this?
It was my idea.
You're kidding.
Yeah. It'll make
a great first episode
of The Asskateers.
Actually, I think they went
with Dumbass.
Oh, damn. I already had
a bunch of t-shirts made up.
What can I say?
Well, still, you got to like
that your son's got
a little entrepreneurial spirit.
Thanks for showing me
the bright side.
No problem.
Memory wipe?
I think I will.
♪ Men. ♪
Looking for Japanese
subs, Cap'n?
What? No, I'm just trying out
these new binoculars.
You're spying on
Rose, aren't you?
It's not spying. It's...
Shut up and leave me alone.
You said you were
going to forget her.
And you said you were going
to move out after a few days.
Don't change the subject.
I'm just trying to get
a glimpse of her husband.
Oh, that's really sad.
Sadder than throwing your back
out trying to pleasure yourself?
I was doing yoga.
Then why were you
wearing lipstick?
And again, don't
change the subject.
I am simply curious to see what
kind of guy Rose would marry.
Oh, well, if
that's the case,
why don't you just go over
there, knock on the door,
and shake the
man's hand?
What would I tell him?
"Hi. I'm Charlie Harper.
Your wife used to stalk me"?
I might leave that part out.
And besides, I'm sure he
already knows about you.
How would he know about me?
Well, it's possible
she told him,
or perhaps he
noticed the tattoo
of your face on her
left butt cheek.
Yeah, I kind of wish
she hadn't done that.
After she takes a hot bath,
I start looking like
Edward James Olmos.
Just go over,
introduce yourself
and welcome him to
the neighborhood.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Bring over a bottle of wine,
little housewarming gift.
Now you're talking.
(clattering)
JAKE and ELDRIDGE:
Geronimo!
(both screaming)
(crashing)
Oh, God. Are you all right?
JAKE:
Mostly.
Did you remember
to get it on video?
ELDRIDGE:
Aw, crap.
♪ Men. ♪
(doorbell rings)
Charlie, what are
you doing here?
I thought I'd stop by
and welcome you guys
to the neighborhood.
No, no. This is a
bad idea. Please go.
But I thought we could
open a bottle of wine
and all get
to know each other.
Listen to me, Charlie.
I love my husband.
I'm building a new life with him
and I won't let you ruin it.
How could I ruin it?
Well, he doesn't
even know you exist,
and I plan on
keeping it that way.
How is that possible?
What about the tattoo?
I added glasses to it and
told him it was Harry Potter.
Now, please get out of here.
Okay, fine.
I'm sorry.
Just so I'm clear,
you and I, we're...?
Over, finished.
Okay.
I get it.
Told you he'd stop by.
♪ Men. ♪
Do you realize how
lucky you are?
You could have
broken your necks.
We took precautions.
You flew off the roof!
In a shopping cart!
What precautions?
We were planning
to land in the ocean.
You missed it by 100 yards.
It's not an exact science, Dad.
Okay, okay. Let's not
dicker over the details.
(both laughing)
He said, "dicker."
I know.
Okay, okay.
I am serious. Okay?
This Dumbass thing
stops right now.
You're the one who told me
I should follow my dreams.
I meant dreams
like "doctor" or "lawyer,"
not "crash test dummy."
"Dr. Jacob Harper."
I like the sound of that.
Hey, doc, what's this on
my nutsack? Is it infected?
Yes. It seems we'll have to
perform a nutsackectomy.
(both chuckling)
Will you two quit
with the cockamamie babble
and focus on what
I am trying to tell you?
He said, "cockamamie."
(both laughing)
He said, "focus."
(laughter)
♪ Men. ♪
(TV plays quietly)
Oh, what's to become
of my son?
Don't worry, Alan.
There'll always be carnivals.
I suppose.
So, how'd it go
with Mr. and Mrs. Manfred Quinn?
I never met him.
Rose told me to get lost.
Wow. That's got to sting a bit.
Yeah, but I understand.
She's happy now, and doesn't
want me screwing it up.
You still love her, don't you?
I guess I do.
Funny how these things turn out,
isn't it?
I mean, eight, nine years ago,
she was just a crazy
one-night stand
who ended up stalking you.
All you wanted
to do was get rid of her.
But the years go by,
and stalking turns
to friendship.
Friendship turns to love.
But it's too late.
She marries another man,
and she's lost to you forever.
Boy, that would make
a great movie, wouldn't it?
Yeah, great.
Want to write it with me?
What?! No!
Well, don't go stealing it.
I mean, you know,
it's your life,
but it's my idea.
(sighs)
Oh, how's this
for a title?
Look Who's Stalking.
Meet the Stalkers.
Avatart.
Are you done?
Yeah.
Although I do think it has
real franchise opportunities.
Could be a sitcom.
Maybe not on a major network,
but, you know, TBS, TNT.
I Love Looney.
Where you going?
I was just spitballin' here.
(quietly chuckling)
I said, "spitballin'."
Oh, God, I want to die.
♪ Men. ♪
(slow, romantic
music plays on TV)
♪ Men. ♪
That has got to be
the worst-looking toupee
I've ever seen.
What the hell
are you doing here?!
You scared the
hell out of me.
Are you crazy,
climbing up on my deck,
snooping around like this?!
I need to talk to you.
Well, I can't
talk to you.
Manny is right inside.
I love you.
It's a little late for that.
I'm sorry. I realize now, Rose,
I can't live without you.
It doesn't matter
what you realize.
I'm married now.
Oh, please, Rose.
Oh, God, Charlie,
why are you doing this
to me? It's so unfair.
I'm begging you.
Just talk to me.
(sighs)
All right.
Manny has to go back into
the office to do some work.
Come back in an hour.
Thank you.
But just to talk.
Of course.
- And can you bring me some
butter brickle ice cream?
- What?
- And marshmallow fluff and sprinkles.
- Sure, whatever you need.
Chocolate sprinkles, not
the multicolored kind.
- Fine.
- I don't know why they even make those.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
(thudding)
Ow!
Son of a bitch!
How do you do that?
Don't lock your knees.
(romantic music plays on TV)
Good news, Manny.
We're getting ice cream.
♪ Men. ♪
You ready
for some more beans?
Bring it on.
(clears throat)
So, I'm thinking we call
this stunt "Fart Rocket."
Nah, I think we need to go with
something more intellectual.
How about
"The Dumbass Assblaster?"
No, you can't use
two "asses" in a row.
It's... redumbnant.
Hey.
What's going on?
I'm just making Eldridge
something to eat.
Really?
Yes, I was peckerish.
You mean peckish.
Fine. If you
want to dicker.
(both laughing)
Good one, dude.
Hey.
What's in the bag?
Butter brickle ice cream
with marshmallow fluff
and chocolate sprinkles.
Oh, Charlie, no.
What?!
"What?!"
Only one person on earth
puts chocolate sprinkles
and marshmallow fluff on
butter brickle ice cream.
Congratulations, Sherlock.
You cracked the case.
She is a married woman, Charlie.
I can't help it. I love her.
Oh, please.
You didn't start loving her
until you found out
you couldn't have her.
So? That doesn't
make it... not love.
But what if her husband
catches you?
Then he shoots me, and you can
have my house and my car.
Go to her, Charlie.
She's waiting.
(sighs)
(thudding)
Ow!
Son of a bitch!
(breaking wind)
JAKE:
Dude, don't waste it.
Squeeze it in!
♪ Men. ♪
(panting)
(grunting)
Not as easy
as it looks, is it?
No.
Is your husband gone?
He just left.
We're alone.
Oh, great.
Wait.
We agreed, just talking.
Right, right, right.
Just talking. Let's talk.
Do you know what Manny said
to me right before he left?
Um... "I love you,
"but it's okay to have
an affair with Charlie,
'cause he's a swell guy
and I'm secretly gay"?
No.
He said, in the whole world,
I'm the only one
who can move him.
Like I said, gay.
How can I betray
a man like that?
I can think of
several ways.
You on top, you on bottom,
everybody facing the TV.
Charlie.
Who moves you,
Rose? Him or me?
I don't know. I'm confused.
I love Manny.
But you and I are soul mates,
like Romeo and Juliet.
Really? Did Romeo ever
chew through the ropes
holding him to a radiator in
a motel outside of Bakersfield
when Juliet was just trying
to give him a birthday surprise?
Birthday surprise? You
were going to brand me.
Branding is the new
piercing, Charlie.
Fine. Pierce me, brand me,
do anything you want.
Anything?
It's just an expression.
Give me another chance, Rose.
No. It's wrong.
Fine. You just say the
word, and I'll go.
Time's up.
(sighing)
I love you.
I love you, too.
You know what this means,
don't you?
I think so.
You're going to have
to kill Manny.
What?!
Kidding.
Just wanted to see
how far you'd go.
♪ Men. ♪
Can I tell you
something, Rose?
Anything.
I've never felt happier
and more at peace
than I do
at this very moment.
Who's being a
little gay now?
(phone chimes)
Oh. It's a text from Manny.
He's on his way home.
You have to go.
When can I see you again?
You can't.
This was a mistake.
How can you say that?
Charlie, I love my husband.
Forget Manny.
Run away with me.
You don't mean that.
I do.
Come on, Charlie.
If you had me to yourself,
you'd be tired of me
within a year.
Then you can go back to Manny.
Everybody wins.
Go.
I love you.
Oh, aren't you the naughty boy
who likes to watch?
♪ Men. ♪
ELDRIDGE:
Hurry up, dude.
I'm about to blow.
Hang on.
Hi. I'm Jake Harper,
and you're about to witness
a little something
we like to call...
"Fumes of Fury."
- Let's do this thing.
- All right.
Remember, if
for some reason
you don't reach the
ocean, just tuck and roll.
Okay, just hurry up.
All right.
Let 'er rip.
(breaking wind,
flame roaring)
Dumbasses.
I can't believe nothing happened.
I wouldn't say that.
I think I cracked my pants.
♪ Men. ♪
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==